<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Epidemic Simulator</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="enter_name_hint">Please enter your name</string>
    <string name="Name_text">Name</string>
    <string name="check_button">Check!</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="rank_button">Ranking</string>
    <string name="set_button">Setting</string>
    <string name="game_title">OSU Epidemic Simulator</string>

    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="rules_button">Rules</string>
    <string name="authors_button">Author Information</string>
    <string name="events_button">Events Information</string>
    <string name="quit_button">Quit</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="body">" As the game starts, you will have five options from which you can choose three. This represents the three categories of supplies you harvested on your way back to your apartment at the start of the pandemic. You only get limited resources. Every day you pass in the game, your physical and mental health drops by 20%. If either of the two reaches 0%, you will die. You can restore physical health (food and water) using the supplies you gain. You can also interact with the items you get (sleep, radio, books...), maybe it will help your mental health. Don't try to escape reality by sleeping. The psychological benefits of sleep are limited. The truly brave one will find another way.\n       The Ohio State University police will come to your rescue. But it might take them 14 days to find you. You need to stay alive when the campus police arrive. Besides, all communications equipment was cut off and permanently unavailable at the start of the outbreak. The only thing you can use is a radio you might get at Caldwell lab. The radio will occasionally hear messages from campus police.\n       You may encounter different events. The impact of each event is different. It all depends on whether you want to turn on the event or not. (events here means you probably can get some resources or some helpers (some buffs))\n       You can use the map to go out and explore. Each exploration will cost 10% of your physical and mental health. You may find something to gain from your exploration. (here we probably use google map or some other hardware like Gyro as our sensor)\n      If you are still alive after 14 days, you will be rescued by the campus police and end 1. If you die within 14 days, you'll have Ending 2 right away. The game has multiple endings (methods of death) waiting for your exploration. "</string>

</resources>